Brenda Beck collection from Tamil Nadu, India
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Performances and songs, 1965; 1975, The following transcripts and recordings have digital content that can be accessed on request on digital carrier afc2017/050_cf11.
  - Ponnivala Annanmar story texts, original, Manuscript (Box-folder 10/1 - 12/5)
    - Annanmar story, AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR20, SR24; 11 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
      Includes the text for Beck's version of the Annanmar tale which she calls the Ponnivala story or Ponnivala Nadu story (for English speakers). She created a 13 hour animation, along with a two-volume graphic novel telling the same story. Continuation of ballad performed by Ramacamy and Palani from AFC 2017/050: SR20. It also contains the recording of the first night of house 97 exorcism.
  - Annanmar story texts, second copy, part 1, Manuscript (Box-folder 12/6 - 14/5)
    - Annanmar, AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR20, SR24; 11 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
      Transcript of the epic Annanmar story transcribed in Tamil pattu by K. Naresh Kumar. The tale is about the twins, Ponnar and Shankar, the sons of a Kongu Vellalar couple, Nellian Kodan (or Kunru Udaiyaan) and his wife Thamarai. They became rulers of Ponni Valanadu in medieval Tamil Nadu, South India, and is credited with saving their people from an invasion. See AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR20. Includes all of the recordings of the Annanmar tale.
  - Concordance for Anannmar story texts, second copy, Manuscript. (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Annanmar, AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR20, SR24; 11 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
      Includes all the recordings of the Annanmar tale.
  - Ramacamy and Palani, Manuscript (Box-folder 15/1-4)
    Transcript of Ramacamy and Palani performing the epic Annanmar tale. Ramacamy is a master storyteller and his nephew Palani is his apprentice.
    - Annanmar, AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR23, SR24; 14 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.; AFC 2017/050: SR77; 1 sound cassette: analog
      Recorded by Brenda Beck, 1965 over a period of 18 nights.
  - Ramacamy and Palani version-notes, Manuscript (Box-folder 15/5)
    Beck's notes on the recording of the Annanmar story performed by Ramacamy and Palani. Includes all the recordings of the Annanmar tale.
    - Annanmar, AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR24; 14 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
      Recorded by Brenda Beck, 1965.
  - Ramacamy and Karuppan- unfinished, Manuscript (Box-folder 15/6-7)
    Transcript of the recording of Ramacamy and Karuppan performing Annanmar. Kaurppan is an alternate singer who sometimes sang alone but sometimes under the leadership and direction of Ramacamy. He was a potter by caste whereas Ramacamy and Palani were barbers. These two communities have a (roughly) similar status locally, but they are definitely different. Sound recordings on 5-inch reel to reel. Includes all the recordings of the Annanmar tale.
    - Annanmar, AFC 2017/050: SR11-SR20, SR24; 14 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
  - Annanmar story singers— biographical information, Manuscript (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Ramacamy basic dictation, Manuscript (Box-folder 15/9 - 16/2)
    Transcript of Ramacamy singing the story of Annanmar. Beck uses this version in her book, The three twins: the telling of a South Indian Folk 1982, where she discusses the difference between oral tradition versus when it is written down.
  - Story Opening A, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/3)
    Includes Annanmar story opening.
  - Story Opening B, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Story Opening C, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Story Opening D, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Story Opening E, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/7)
  - H version (The three twins, 1982) book, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/8)
  - F version (The three twins, 1982) book, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Caktikannal version, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Periya KaaNTi version, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Kummi songs, Nadar house 22, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/12)
    - Chettiar and other short stories and songs, AFC 2017/050: SR30; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
  - Kummi songs for Valliamman, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/13)
    - Chettiar and other short stories and songs, AFC 2017/050: SR30; 1 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
  - Cami Padal, lullaby song, August 2, 1966, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Cami Padal, kavadi song, August 2, 1966, Manuscript (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Kovalan and other short stories, AFC 2017/050: SR31, SR34; 2 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
- Series 4: Family histories, 1965-1966
  - Subseries 1: Caste, The following transcripts and recordings have digital content that can be accessed on request on digital carrier afc2017/050_cf11.
    - Caste stories
      - Cenkuta Mutaliyar story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Maamari Naataar story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Mutaliyar (caste) story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Mutaliyar sub castes split-up story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Olapalayam Kannakapillai story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Ookacaadi Pandarams, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Palani Mutaliyar story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Veettuva Gounder story, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Caste interaction charts
      - Caste to caste food exchange, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/9)
      - Food exchange in Olapalayam—charts, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Nilakkotai ranking and social information, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Subseries 2: Olapalayam and neighborhood census
    - Houses 1-10B, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Houses 10C-21B, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Houses 22-36, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Houses 37-52, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Houses 53-68, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Houses 71-87, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/17)
    - Houses 88-100, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/18)
    - Gannapuram kiramam hamlet list and map, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/19)
    - Hamlet household counts by kulam and caste, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Household survey Olapalayam houses 18, 93, 94 and 40c, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Kadai vidi household survey, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Koluncikaattuvalasu households, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Maataari hamlet households—Pusarivalasu, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/24)
    - Maataari hamlet households—Sangangadu, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/25)
    - Coimbatore House-to-house caste survey, Manuscript (Box-folder 17/26-28)
      Oversized materials separated to Box 46.
    - Map of Olapalayam, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/1)
      Includes a photocopy of the map of Olapalayam identifying house numbers. See Box 46 for original oversize map.
    - Map of houses in the census, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/2)
      Includes a map showing houses in the census, by number and location.
    - Murugangadu household list, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/3)
      Includes a household list written in Tamil.
    - Names of households in Olapalayam, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/4)
      Includes the names of households in Olapalayam by house numbers.
    - Names of reference for Olapalayam households, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/5)
      Includes the names of people referred to in a conversation by Sundaram, February 11, 1966.
    - Olapalayam households by caste, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/6)
      List of caste names and house numbers.
    - Olapalayam households by caste and shared fields, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/7)
      Includes household names from a survey of economic conditions by K. Raju Govti, March 20, 1965.
    - Olapalayam land registration and field maps, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Olapalayam landowners, Karnam records, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Ownership of fields in Olapalayam by house number, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/10)
      Includes information collected by Sengotayan and Sundaram, June 1966. In English.
    - Pachapalayam household list, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Pariayar hamlet households and map, Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/12)
      Oversize map separated to Box 46.
    - Pusarivalasu household list, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Three Olapalayam maps from BB D.Phil thesis, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/14)
      Includes letter sized photocopies of maps of Olapalayam, 1965. Maps show the alignment among the Olapalayam residents and the Kavuntar clans.
  - Subseries 3: Regional Kongu structures
    Include four titled families of Kongu
    - Cengarandampalayam Pattakkarar story, February 14, 1966, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/15)
    - Kangayam nadu formal subdivisions, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/16)
      See Box 18, Folder 29 for related information.
    - Kangayam natu story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/17)
      Transcript of Kangayam natu-stone inscription from Chidambaram. The story can be found in a book, Growth of Tamil Prose, 1968.
    - Kadaiyur Pattakarar story, February 14, 1966, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/18)
    - Paraiyakottai Pattakkarar story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/19)
      Includes the story of Palaiyakattai Pattarara, February 14, 1966.
    - Pattakkarar requirements for free public work, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/20)
      Requirements are in Tamil.
    - Putur Pattakkarar story, February 14, 1966, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/21)
    - Settlement of Kongu natu story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/22)
      Transcript of the story about the Settlement of Kongu Nadu as given in an unpublished Kuravanji Palani Puluvanar Tiruppur, January 23, 1966. See Box 18, Folder 23 for second part of story.
    - Settlement of Kongunadu story 2, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/23)
      See Box 18, Folder 22 for related materials.
    - Four PaTTakarar families, story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/24)
      Transcript of the Palaiyakottai Pattakarar, story, February 14, 1966.
- Series 5: Family lineage histories, 1966; 1969, The following transcripts and recordings have digital content that can be accessed on request on digital carrier afc2017/050_cf11.
  Family histories also include temple rights.
  - Aacaari genealogy, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/25)
    Includes Aacaari genealogy from aasani palm leaf manuscript. Information from house 97, January 20, 1966.
  - Basket Kuravar groups, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/26)
  - Cenguntam Mutaliyar groups, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/27)
    Includes description of Medeliyar sub caste Palani Puluvanar Tirruppur.
  - Kingship interview with Sundaram's brother, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Division of temple rights, Sundaram's family, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/29)
    Includes the formal division of temple rights by Sundaram's family.
  - Gannapuram Gounder kulams, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Gannapuram Othala clan origin, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/31)
    Includes the Kannapuram KavuNTon of the otala clan (name unknown).
  - Gannapuram Othala kulam story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/32)
    Includes the story of Ponnambale Gr., Othala Kulam and Kuppusamy Gr., Rettivalasm, June 14, 1966.
  - Gannapuram rulers in Sangam literature, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/33)
    Includes information pertaining to the Gannapuram rulers who are mentioned in the Sangam literature.
  - Gounder kulam names, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/34)
    Includes Gounder kulam names from books.
  - Gounder kulam names and origins, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/35)
    Includes information provided by Palani Puluvanar, Nanjappa High Sch., Tiruppur, January 23, 1966.
  - Gounder Kulam names from books, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/36)
    List of references to kulam names in books.
  - Gounder Kulams of Kangayam Natu, June 13th, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/37)
  - Kannakapillai Family and Olapalayam, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/38)
    - Kinship recording and other short stories, AFC 2017/050:SR32; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
      Recording of the story of the 3 origin kulams as told by Muttusamy, June 14, 1966.
  - Kanavaala Gounder Kulam story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/39)
  - Kannakku Pillai of Olapalayam family history, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/40)
  - Kilvani Mutaliyar information and Kamachiamman song, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/41)
  - Koindappa Pandaram genealogy, Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/42)
    Includes a drawing of the family tree, Gannapmam: Koindappa Pandaram, January 22, 1966.
  - Kuruvan (basket makers) map and details, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/43)
    Includes information on Nachi Kuruvan, Rettivalasm, March 15, 1966.
  - Maataari information, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/44)
  - Maataari Kulam information, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/45)
  - Maathaari (Totti) kulams and other info, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/46)
  - Nadar kulams, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/47)
    Includes the 2nd copy of the kulam, March 15, 1969.
  - Navakoti Chettiar of Kaveripunpattinam family history, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/48)
  - Non-Olapalayam key Gounder kulam genealogies, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/49)
    Includes diagrams of different family trees.
  - Olapalayam Kannakapillai information, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/50)
  - Ootaala Gounder Kulam story, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/51-53)
  - Palani Paraiyan Genealogy, Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/54)
    Includes diagram of family tree, December 12, 1966.
  - Pandaram lineage—caste line, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/55)
    Story recorded on February 14, 1966.
  - Pulavar attached to ancient Kings—legend, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/56)
    Story recorded on January 23, 1966.
  - Reference terms—various Olapalayam Gounder families, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/57)
    Includes the names of people referred to in a conversation conducted by Sundaram, February 11, 1966. Names are arranged by birth names first followed by caste affiliation in parenthesis.
  - Sivanmalai—songs about temple rights, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/58)
    Transcript. Recorded on June 13, 1966.
  - Story of how the Kanavala kulam came to Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/59)
  - Story of how the Maamari Nadars came to Kongu natu, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/60)
  - Story of poets attached to ancient kings, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/61)
  - unidentified page, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/62)
    Includes a page from unidentified source.
  - The three original Kulams of Kannapuram Gounder, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/63)
  - Udaiyar groups, Manuscript (Box-folder 18/64)
- Series 6: Ritual and practices, 1965-1969; 1976-1977
  - Subseries 1: Temple maps
    - Angalamman Utaiyur Temple, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Annanmar Temple in Lingappa Gountanvalasu, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Annanmar Temple on Kodumudi to Erode road, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Jafna Temple maps, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Maps of Olapalayam and neighborhood, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/5)
    - Temple maps 112-127, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/6)
    - Temple map—supplement -A series, nos. 1-63 A, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Temple maps (additions) M24 and M28, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Temple maps basic series, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/9-10)
  - Subseries 2: Temple rituals
    Contains temple rituals—plus inscriptions and related stories
    - About Vastu, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Bananas and cocoanuts in puja rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/12)
      Transcript. See page 16 in Black-and-white negatives index for images.
    - Batirakaliamman puja, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Cucinaram Vishnu Temple inscription, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Drawing of Pillar— Mantisvaran Temple 3, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Ganesh placement in temples—notes, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Gannapuram Shiva Temple inscriptions, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Invitation to gods to attend Maariyamman fire pot dance, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/18)
    - Kangayam natu Siva Temple—old songs, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/19)
    - Karuppanasami and Kannimar Kumbavisekam in Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/20)
    - Kumbavisekam for Murugan, Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/21)
    - Kumbavisekam for the Kannimar in Pappani, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Kumbavisekam Rituals—general, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Mandisvaran Temple, Gannapuram, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Murugan worship expenses, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Number of gods in a temple—notes, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Pongal ritual for Maariyamman, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/27)
    - Retnamurthi Temple rights, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/28)
    - Retnamurthi Temple story, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/29)
    - Rituals for Mantisvaran Temple, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/30)
    - Siva Temple wedding festival songs, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/31)
    - Temple orientation—various gods, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/32)
    - Use of a mirror in rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 19/33)
  - Subseries 3: Spirit possessions
    Transcripts of spirit possession, 1969
    - 2nd Aacari spirit possession House 97, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/1-2)
      - Peeye excorcism, AFC 2017/050: SR26; 2 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
        Recording of a spirit exorcism of an Aacari girl. The exorcism was performed over a period of three days. The recording contains audio of the 2nd and 3rd night. The first night can be found on AFC 2017/050: SR25. Recorded on November 18-19th, 1965. AFC 2017/050: SR34 has wedding songs from the same house 97.
    - Aacaari House 97 spirit exorcism, 1969, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/3-4)
      - Peeye excorcism, AFC 2017/050: SR24; 2 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
        Recording contains audio of the first night of a spirit exorcism of an Aacari girl who was possessed by seven spirits. Notes on AFC 2017/050: SR20 indicates that it contains audio of the spirit possession. Audio recordings of the possession can also be heard on AFC 2017/050: 26. It contains the first night of the recording of the spirit exorcism. Recorded by Beck, November 17th, 1965.
    - Aacaari House 97, evil spirit exorcism, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/5-7)
      - Peeye excorcism, AFC 2017/050: SR26; 2 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
        Recording contains audio of a spirit exorcism of an Aacari girl for the 2nd and 3rd night performed over a period of three days. The first night can be found on AFC 2017/050: SR25. May be duplicate of previous folder. Additional recordings can be heard on AFC 2017/050: SR20 and AFC 2017/050: SR26. Recorded by Beck, November 18-19th, 1965.
    - Gounder and Pandaram possession, Mariyamman festival, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/8)
      - Short stories and songs, AFC2017/050: SR29; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
    - Spirit possession of a Gounder girl in house 56, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/9-10)
      - Excorcism, AFC 2017/050: SR31; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
        Recorded by Brenda Beck, September, 14, 1965.
    - Maataari possession, Pusarivalasu, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/11)
      Transcript, 1966.
      - Kumbam to shrine and other stories, AFC 2017/050: SR28; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
    - Maataari possession, Olapalayam, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/12)
      - Kumbam to shrine and other stories, AFC 2017/050: SR28; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
    - Nadar possession at Olapalayam, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/13)
      Transcript, June 14, 1966.
      - Kumbam to shrine, Chettiar story and other stories, AFC 2017/050: SR28, SR30; 2 sound tape reels; analog; 5 in.
    - Possessed priest with fire pot, Mariyamman festival, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/14)
      Transcript. It details the activities of temple goers during the festival.
      - Kumbam to shrine and other stories, AFC 2017/050: SR28; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
    - Possession of several bringing kumban from well, Makaliamman Festival, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/15)
      Transcript. Includes the activities of temple goers during the festival.
      - Kumbam to shrine and other stories, AFC 2017/050: SR28; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
    - Possessions at Maariyamman Festival, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/16)
      - Kumbam to shrine and other stories, AFC 2017/050: SR28; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
        Recorded by Brenda Beck, January 4th-6th, 1966. Recording includes the activities of temple goers during the festival. Also includes Maariyamman Festival and the activities surrounding visiting the temple and spirit possession.
    - Utaiyar lineage festival possession, Papani, Manuscript (Box-folder 20/17)
      - Chettiar story and songs, AFC 2017/050: SR30; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
        Recorded by Brenda Beck, 1966. Recording includes the activities of temple goers during the festival.
  - Subseries 4: Coming of age rituals
    Transcripts of different coming of age ceremonies. See PH01-03 for graphic images.
    - Gounder girl ceremony, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Gounder Pandaram girl, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Udaiyar girl A and B ceremonies, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Utaiyar, Olapalayam main day, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Utaiyar, Olapalayam previous day, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Subseries 5: Funeral
    - Dirges, Oppari
      - Paraiyan sequence, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/6)
        Transcript, November 26, 1965.
        - Annanmar, Nyanacaguntari and funeral songs, AFC 2017/050: SR20; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
      - House 35, Nadar songs, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/7)
      - House 37-38, Pandaram songs, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/8)
      - House 45 Gounder songs, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/9)
      - Rettivalasu women, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/10)
        - Short stories from Rettivalasu, other stories and crying songs, AFC 2017/050: SR29; 1 sound tape reel; analog; 5 in.
  - Subseries 6: Ceremonies
    - Aiyar Brahman, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Aiyar rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Ciirvaani Mutaliyar, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/13)
      - Families, temples and activities in Olapalayam, AFC 2017/050: PH01-04
        See page 67 in Black-and-white negatives index for Mutaliyar wedding ceremony, October 3, 1965.
    - Etupparar Maataari, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Rites for married older Gounder women, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Gounder funeral for unmarried man over sixteen, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Gounder rituals for women, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Gounder ceremonies, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/18)
      - Temples and village activities, AFC 2017/050: PH01-06
        See page 91 in Black-and-white negatives index for new born child ceremony for a Gounder family.
    - Gounder ritual for an unmarried man over sixteen, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Kilvani Mutaliyar death rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Konku Maataari death rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Maataari Cakkiliyar, 1st copy, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/22)
    - Maataari Cakkiliyar, 2nd copy, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/23)
    - Maataari Cakkiliyar rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/24)
    - Pootanar Maataari, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/25)
    - Rituals for those who die a sudden death or bizarre death, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/26)
    - Udaiyar, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/27)
    - Udaiyar male rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/28)
    - Utailyar death rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/29)
    - Veedar, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/30)
    - Veetan death rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/31)
  - Subseries 7: Weddings
    - Tali Drawings and details (wedding necklaces), Manuscript (Box-folder 21/32)
    - (Vellala) Gounder rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/33)
    - Aacaari rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/34)
    - Acaari ceremonies, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/35)
    - Comparison chart— various wedding ceremonies, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/36)
    - Kannakku Pillai wedding songs, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/37)
    - Kuruvan rituals, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/38)
    - Maataari girl second marriage, Manuscript (Box-folder 21/39)